Get tactical, Marines!
Major ? Allez sur ce cargo et capturez-moi ce Prophète du Regret.
This is the only place on Earth the Covenant decided to land. That prophet is going to tell us why.
You heard the man, boys. It's time for some hazard pay!
Thirty seconds out. Stand by to…
Whoah!
Status!
Sir? O'Brien's down.
We lost our pilots, too.
Grab their tags and ammo.
Sarge!
We better get moving.
Agreed. We'll find better cover in those buildings.
Butkis, you take point.
Hello!
Sniper, third floor, left.
Here…let me give them my "Welcome to Earth" gift basket!
Whoah!
Damn, where is he?
Anybody see him?
Take him, guys!
Cook the bastard.
Second squad, this is Cortana. What is your status, over.
We're operational, ma'am…barely.
Our pilots didn't make it.
Find a hole, stay put. We'll come to you.