We're going in.
Get tactical, Marines!
You heard the man, boys! It's time for some hazard pay!
Thirty seconds out. Stand by...
Whoa.
Huh?
Status!
Sir, O'Brien's down. We lost our pilots, too.
Grab their tags and ammo.
Sarge, we better get moving.
Agreed.
We'll find better cover in those buildings.
Butkus, you take point.
Hello!
Sniper, third floor left.
Here, let me give him my welcome-to-Earth gift basket.
Here, see what I have?
Damn! Where is he?
Anybody see him?
Well, I'm not sure about that.
I'm not sure of anything.
How are you, O'Brien?
I'm not very well, sir...
Nobody on the scene?
We'll take a short walk around.
Take him, guys!
Cook the bastard.
Second squad, this is Cortana. What is your status? Over.
We're operational, ma'am. Barely. Our pilots didn't make it.
Find a hole. Stay put. We'll come to you.