1
00:00:52,592 --> 00:00:53,409
What's that?

2
00:00:53,664 --> 00:00:54,441
A beacon.

3
00:00:54,901 --> 00:00:55,615
What's it doing?

4
00:00:55,797 --> 00:00:58,709
Communicating at superluminal speeds with a frequency of -

5
00:00:58,876 --> 00:01:00,265
Communicating with what?

6
00:01:00,431 --> 00:01:01,973
The other installations.

7
00:01:02,147 --> 00:01:02,691
Show me.

8
00:01:03,096 --> 00:01:13,375
Fail-safe protocol: in the event of unexpected shut-down, the entire system will move to standby status. All remaining platforms are now ready for remote activation.

9
00:01:13,590 --> 00:01:15,956
Remote activation? From here?

10
00:01:16,152 --> 00:01:17,384
Don't be ridiculous.

11
00:01:17,535 --> 00:01:19,432
Listen, tinker-bell, don't make me -

12
00:01:19,565 --> 00:01:23,403
Then where? Where would someone go to activate the other rings?

13
00:01:23,578 --> 00:01:25,371
Why...the Ark, of course.

14
00:01:25,919 --> 00:01:28,597
And where, Oracle, is that?

15
00:01:37,241 --> 00:01:39,946
We've got a new contact, unknown classification!

16
00:01:40,227 --> 00:01:42,456
It isn't one of ours. Take it out!

17
00:01:42,600 --> 00:01:44,361
This is Spartan one-one-seven!

18
00:01:44,779 --> 00:01:46,143
Can anyone hear me, over?!

19
00:01:46,310 --> 00:01:47,608
Isolate that signal!

20
00:01:48,024 --> 00:01:51,286
Master Chief? You mind telling me what you're doing on that ship?!

21
00:01:52,760 --> 00:01:55,710
Sir. Finishing this fight.

