1
00:00:05,945 --> 00:00:07,813
I do not trust you.

2
00:00:09,092 --> 00:00:12,159
He may... but I do not.

3
00:00:12,928 --> 00:00:13,762
Noted.

4
00:00:14,246 --> 00:00:18,480
My friend's trust is not the issue today, Spartan Locke.

5
00:00:20,063 --> 00:00:23,196
It is my trust you must earn

6
00:00:23,486 --> 00:00:24,020
Arbiter.

7
00:00:26,687 --> 00:00:30,154
You are a hunter, yes? A seeker of things.

8
00:00:30,348 --> 00:00:34,348
That's not the official job title. But it's close enough.

9
00:00:34,658 --> 00:00:37,225
And now you hunt other Spartans?

10
00:00:37,540 --> 00:00:42,107
I'm not so much hunting a Spartan, as I am hunting the Spartan

11
00:00:46,690 --> 00:00:47,790
You seek...

12
00:00:48,003 --> 00:00:49,537
one-one-seven

13
00:00:49,691 --> 00:00:52,858
I was not told the identity of your prey.

14
00:00:53,136 --> 00:00:55,637
That's why I'm sharing it with you now.

15
00:00:56,154 --> 00:00:58,022
We're talking about trust, after all.

16
00:01:00,238 --> 00:01:07,741
May I ask you something? Your people used to call him "Demon." Was an insult or a complement?

17
00:01:08,105 --> 00:01:13,366
...An insult, to be sure. But one with a modicum of respect.

18
00:01:14,050 --> 00:01:22,061
He was indeed my enemy. But in time, I named him ally, even friend.

19
00:01:23,052 --> 00:01:27,494
The events which forged this bond were...  complicated.

