1
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:03,670
Arbiter, we are nearing the target.

2
00:00:04,200 --> 00:00:05,300
Prepare for action.

3
00:00:10,000 --> 00:00:11,950
What do you call him, Spartan Locke?

4
00:00:13,180 --> 00:00:14,530
I don't understand the question.

5
00:00:15,200 --> 00:00:17,810
117, the Master Chief.

6
00:00:18,380 --> 00:00:21,420
He is not your friend. Is he your foe?

7
00:00:21,980 --> 00:00:25,450
He's gone AWOL and the UNSC wants him back.

8
00:00:25,680 --> 00:00:27,360
I'm going to bring him home.

9
00:00:29,120 --> 00:00:32,280
I admire your sense of duty, Spartan.

10
00:00:32,281 --> 00:00:33,920
Covenant forces incoming.

11
00:00:34,200 --> 00:00:37,370
But if he has left the fold, he has his reasons.

12
00:00:37,940 --> 00:00:41,800
I'm sure he does, Arbiter. And I intend to find out what they are.

