1
00:00:01,731 --> 00:00:02,602
We're going in.

2
00:00:04,170 --> 00:00:05,806
Get tactical, Marines!

3
00:00:07,570 --> 00:00:10,995
You heard the man, boys. It's time for some hazard pay!

4
00:00:12,712 --> 00:00:14,680
30 seconds out. Stand by to...

5
00:00:18,546 --> 00:00:19,046
Whoah!

6
00:01:00,816 --> 00:01:01,316
Status!

7
00:01:02,064 --> 00:01:04,040
Sir? O'Brien's down.

8
00:01:04,785 --> 00:01:06,418
We lost our pilots, too.

9
00:01:07,237 --> 00:01:08,708
Grab their tags and ammo.

10
00:01:08,959 --> 00:01:09,459
Sarge!

11
00:01:10,463 --> 00:01:11,657
We better get moving.

12
00:01:12,332 --> 00:01:15,094
Agreed. We'll find better cover in those buildings.

13
00:01:15,897 --> 00:01:17,462
Butkis, you take point.

14
00:01:40,269 --> 00:01:40,769
Hello!

15
00:01:42,174 --> 00:01:43,882
Sniper, third floor, left.

16
00:01:43,967 --> 00:01:47,233
Here... let me give them my "Welcome to Earth" gift basket!

17
00:02:13,899 --> 00:02:14,399
Whoah!

18
00:02:18,697 --> 00:02:19,798
Damn, where is he?

19
00:02:27,660 --> 00:02:28,628
Anybody see him?

20
00:02:45,196 --> 00:02:46,216
Take him, guys!

21
00:02:48,678 --> 00:02:49,834
Cook the bastard.

22
00:02:55,812 --> 00:02:58,724
Second squad, this is Cortana. What is your status, over.

23
00:02:59,038 --> 00:03:00,903
We're operational, ma'am... barely.

24
00:03:01,021 --> 00:03:02,208
Our pilots didn't make it.

25
00:03:02,312 --> 00:03:04,779
Find a hole, stay put. We'll come to you.

